南充。
是二零二一年初中学业水平考试
英语听力测试。
第一节，听下面五段短对话，每段对话后有一个小题，
从题中所给的
,B I hear you are enjoying life at your new school, Elisa.
三个选项中。
选出最佳选项，并在答题卡上将该项涂黑。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话读两遍。
What's your favorite subject?
I still like math and geography, but now I like science best.
I hear you are enjoying life at your new school, Elisa.
What's your favorite subject?
I still like math and geography, but now I like science best.
It's time for bed,
It's already ten o 'clock.
Dad, just a minute.
I'm watching a talk show.
I'll be in bed in twenty minutes.
It's time for bed, Kathy.
It's already ten o
Dad, just a minute.
I'm watching a talk show.
I'll be in bed in twenty minutes.
May I borrow these three books, Miss Stin?
I'm afraid not, Bob.
You borrowed one yesterday, and you know each student can only borrow three at most.
May I borrow these three books, Miss Stin?
I'm afraid not, Bob.
You borrowed one yesterday, and you know each student can only borrow three at most.
I feel very sad.
I can't understand why my father always seems to be kinder to others than to his own
son. You just don't understand him.
He has a heart full of love.
He's strict with you just because he loves you.
I feel very sad.
I can't understand why my father always seems to be kinder to others than to his own
son. You just don't understand him.
He has a heart full of love.
He's strict with you just because he loves you.
第二节。
听下面五段长对话或独白，每段对话或独白后有几个小题，
从题中所给的
B, and and After each conversation the white, several questions.
三个选项中选出。
最佳选项，并在答题卡上将该项涂黑。
听每段对话或独白前，你将有时间阅读各个小题，每小题五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读。
两遍。
听第六段材料，回答第六至第七两个小题。
现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读下面两个小题。
After there several questions.
Tony, your face looks a little bit red.
What's the matter?
I don't feel well, and my head really hurts.
Oh, you'd better go to the doctor right now.
Um, but what about my lessons?
Don't worry, I can help you with your lessons.
Thank you, Mrs.
Tony, your face looks a little bit red.
What's the matter?
I don't feel well, and my head really hurts.
Oh, you'd better go to the doctor right now.
Um, but what about my lessons?
Don't worry, I can help you with your lessons.
Thank you, Mrs.
听第七段材料，回答第八至第十三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读下面三个小题。
Which bank? There are two in the neighborhood, Panda Bank and Green Bank.
I want to get some money from Panda Bank.
It's near the local shopping center, City Mall.
How can I get there?
I have no knowledge of this area.
Go along New Street and turn left at the first crossing.
Walk along Center Street until you reach the traffic lights.
Turn right and you'll see City Mall on your right.
Panda Bank is next to City Mall.
Sounds so difficult.
How far is it from here?
About 10 minutes walk.
I can draw a map for you.
Thank you very much.
Can you tell me how to get to the bank, please?
Which bank? There are two in the neighborhood, Panda Bank and Green Bank.
I want to get some money from Panda Bank.
It's near the local shopping center, City Mall.
How can I get there?
I have no knowledge of this area.
Go along New Street and turn left at the first crossing.
Walk along Center Street until you reach the traffic lights.
Turn right and you'll see City Mall on your right.
Panda Bank is next to City Mall.
so difficult. How far is it from here?
About 10 minutes walk.
I can draw a map for you.
Thank you very much.
听第八段材料，回答第十一至第十三三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读下面三。
三个小题。
March 21, April 12,
and April 22.
chose the earliest one.
OK. How many visitors are coming?
18 or 19?
They said 18 at first, but they changed to 16 this morning.
Good. We have one week to get everything ready.
Here are my suggestions.
On the first day, we'll have a welcome party.
Then they can visit the factories on the second and third days.
Since the visitors want to about how to deal with wastewater,
we may ask Mr.
Goodman to give them a talk about it on the third afternoon.
That would be nice.
What about the last two days?
I have a tour in Langzhong.
Why not take them to Langzhong Ancient Town?
I'm sure they'll enjoy themselves there.
Good idea. One of the visitors is coming, Michael.
They have three dates to choose.
March 21, April 12,
and April 22.
They chose the earliest one.
OK. How many visitors are coming?
18 or 19?
They said 18 at first, but they changed to 16 this morning.
Good. We have one week to get everything ready.
Here are my suggestions.
On the first day, we'll have a welcome party.
Then they can visit the factories on the second and third days.
Since the visitors want to about how to deal with wastewater,
we may ask Mr.
Goodman to give them a talk about it on the third afternoon.
That would be nice.
What about the last two days?
I have a tour in Langzhong.
Why not take them to Langzhong Ancient Town?
I'm sure they'll enjoy themselves there.
Good idea. Welcome to our Tings show.
听第九段材料，回答第十四至第十六三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读下面三个小题。
Can you tell me about your job, Dr.
Yes, of course.
Many students write to me and ask me how to solve their problems.
I always give them my advice.
What problems do they have?
Some students don't have much free time because they have to take so many after
-school classes. I agree.
Sometimes they have to spend most of their free time studying.
What do you think about it?
It can cause a lot of stress for students.
Too much pressure is not good for children's development.
They should have time to relax and think of themselves too.
What suggestions do you usually offer them?
I often advise them to talk to their parents.
Does that help?
Yes, it works.
Most parents are understanding.
That's great. Welcome to our Tings show.
Can you tell me about your job, Dr.
Yes, of course.
Many students write to me and ask me how to solve their problems.
I always give them my advice.
What problems do they have?
Some students don't have much free time because they have to take so many after
-school classes. I agree.
Sometimes they have to spend most of their free time studying.
What do you think about it?
It can cause a lot of stress for students.
Too much pressure is not good for children's development.
They should have time to relax and think of themselves too.
What suggestions do you usually offer them?
I often advise them to talk to their parents.
Does that help?
Yes, it works.
Most parents are understanding.
That's great. you.
听第十段材料，回答第十七至第二十四个小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间阅读下面四个小题。
I'm a plastic bottle.
A week ago I was on a supermarket shelf.
I had a normal life and felt really happy.
Then a tall woman picked me up and drank the water inside me.
She threw me into a bin.
I have never felt so empty in my life.
Early the next morning a man took me out of the bin.
He threw me and the other rubbish into the back of a truck.
Then I was pushed together with the rest of the rubbish.
Soon I became much thinner.
I slept for a while.
When I woke up I found myself in a terrible place.
Everything around me was ugly and had terrible smells.
I felt afraid.
I kept hoping that I would be moved somewhere else.
Then huge trucks came and covered us with earth.
I asked another bottle what would happen to us.
He said that we would never leave this terrible crowded place but would have to stay
here for thousands of years.
Why can't they reuse or recycle us?
cried. I'm a plastic bottle.
A week ago I was on a supermarket shelf.
I had a normal life and felt really happy.
Then a tall woman picked me up and drank the water inside me.
She threw me into a bin.
I have never felt so empty in my life.
Early the next morning a man took me out of the bin.
He threw me and the other rubbish into the back of a truck.
Then I was pushed together with the rest of the rubbish.
Soon I became much thinner.
I slept for a while.
When I woke up I found myself in a terrible place.
Everything around me was ugly and had terrible smells.
I felt afraid.
I kept hoping that I would be moved somewhere else.
Then huge trucks came and covered us with earth.
I asked another bottle what would happen to us.
He said that we would never leave this terrible crowded place but would have to stay
here for thousands of years.
Why can't they reuse or recycle us?
I cried. That's
听力测试到此结束。